Lumbard, Eliot H.; Papers apap071
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Publications: Harm to Each Other: Crime and Crime Control in America, 1956-1996; 11.6 cubic ft.
  - Research: Chapter 7 - "Police and Their Communities," Detection- Criminal Investigation, 1965-1968 (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - Research: Chapter 7 - "Police and Their Communities," General Police- Newsclippings, and Press Releases, 1967-1969; Undated (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - Research: Chapter 7 - "Police and Their Communities," Research, Handwritten Notes, Undated (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - Research: Chapter 7 - "Police and Their Communities," Info. Sharing, 1967; Undated (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - Research: Chapter 7- "Police and Their Communities," The Lot of the Cop, 1966-1969; Undated (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - Research: Chapter 7- "Police and Their Communities," Newark, NJ Police Department (1 of 2), 1967-1969 (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - Research: Chapter 7- "Police and Their Communities," Newark, NJ Police Department (2 of 2), 1967-1969 (Box 7, Folder 30)
  - Research: Chapter 7 - "Police and Their Communities", Newark PD Arrest Records (1 of 2), 1959-1968; Undated (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Research: Chapter 7 - "Police and Their Communities," Newark PD Arrest Records (2 of 2), 1959-1968; Undated (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Research: Chapter 7 - "Police and Their Communities," Newark PD Internal Annual Report, 1967 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Research: Chapter 7 - "Police and Their Communities," New York City Patrolmen's Benevolent Association/ Police and Politics, 1968-1969 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Research: Chapter 7 - "Police and Their Communities," New York City Police Department, 1959-1969 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Research: Chapter 7 - "Police and Their Communities," New York City Police Department Annual Reports/Community Relations, 1966-1968 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Research: Chapter 7 - "Police and Their Communities," New York City Police Department- Community Relations (1 of 2), 1958-1969 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Research: Chapter 7 - "Police and Their Communities," New York City Police Department- Community Relations (2 of 2), 1958-1969 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Research: Chapter 7 - "Police and Their Communities," New York State Police/ State Highway Patrol, 1967; 1969 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Research: Chapter 7 - "Police and Their Communities," Police Communications, 1968-1969 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Research: Chapter 7 - "Police Depts. and Communities", Police Departments Rochester and Newark, 1967-1971; Undated (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Research: Chapter 7 - "Police and Their Communities," Police Fragmentation/Consolidation, 1967-1969; Undated (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Research: Chapter 7 - "Police and Their Communities," Police - Summary, 1960-1968; Undated (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Research: Chapter 7 - "Police and Their Communities," Police Training, 1968-1969 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Research: Chapter 7 - "Police and Their Communities," Police's Role, 1966-1969 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Research: Chapter 7 - "Police and Their Communities," Report by EHL on the Essex County Criminal Justice System and Flyer on the Mob, 1967; Undated (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Research: Chapter 7 - "Police and their Communities" Rochester PD (1 of 2), 1962-1969 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Research: Chapter 7 - "Police and Their Communities," Rochester PD (2 of 2), 1962-1969 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Research: Chapter 7 - "Police and Their Communities," Sheriffs, 1966-1967 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Research: Chapter 8 - "Lawyers", 1969 (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Research: Chapter 8 - "Lawyers," Criminal Defense/Legal Aid, 1962-1969; Undated (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Research: Chapter 8 "Lawyers", DA's Office, Complaint Room Procedures Manual, 1968 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Research: Chapter 8- "Lawyers," New York City's DA Office, 1966-1969; Undated (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Research: Chapter 8 - "Lawyers," Prosecution, 1966-1969 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Research: Chapter 9 - "Court and Law," American Bar Assoc.- Minimum Standards for Criminal Justice Project, 1968-1969; Undated (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Research: Chapter 9 - "Courts and Law", Bail, 1969 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Research: Chapter 9 - "Courts and Law," Big Brother Inc., 1968-1969 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Research: Chapter 9 - "Courts and Law", The Bill of Rights and the 5th Amendment, 1965-1969 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Research: Chapter 9 - "Courts and Law," Chief Justice W. Burger, 1969 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Research: Chapter 9 - "Courts and Law," Conclusions, 1967-1969; Undated (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Research: Chapter 9 - "Courts and Law," Confessions, 1967-1968 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Research: Chapter 9 - "Courts and Law," Criminal Courts (1 of 2), 1963-1969; Undated (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Research: Chapter 9 - "Courts and Law," Criminal Courts (2 of 3), 1963-1969; Undated (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Research: Chapter 9 - "Courts and Law," Criminal Courts (3 of 3), 1963-1969; Undated (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Research: Chapter 9 - "Courts and Law," Criminal Courts, 1969; Undated (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Research: Chapter 9 - "Courts and Law," Death Penalty, 1966-1969 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Research: Chapter 9 - "Courts and Law," Final Review, 1968; Undated (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Research: Chapter 9 - "Courts and Law," In Cold Blood, 1966; Undated (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Research: Chapter 9 - "Courts and Law," Journal Articles and Newsclippings (1 of 2), 1963-1968; Undated (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Research: Chapter 9 - "Courts and Law," Journal Articles and Newsclippings (2 of 2), 1963-1968; Undated (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - Research: Chapter 9 - "Court and Law," Judge Thomas Weaver (NYC Criminal Court), 1968-1969 (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - Research: Chapter 9 - "Courts and Law," Juvenile Delinquency (1 of 4), 1956; Undated (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - Research: Chapter 9 - "Courts and Law," Juvenile Delinquency (2 of 4), 1956; 1966-1968; Undated (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - Research: Chapter 9 - "Courts and Law," Juvenile Delinquency (3 of 4), 1956; 1965-1968; Undated (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - Research: Chapter 9 - "Courts and Law," Juvenile Delinquency (4 of 4), 1956; 1965-1969; Undated (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - Research: Chapter 9 - "Courts and Law," Juveniles (1 of 4), 1965-1969 (Box 9, Folder 25)
  - Research: Chapter 9 - "Courts and Law," Juveniles (2 of 4), 1965-1969 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Research: Chapter 9 - "Courts and Law," Juveniles (3 of 4), 1965-1969 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Research: Chapter 9 - "Courts and Law," Juveniles (4 of 4), 1965-1969 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Research: Chapter 9 - "Court and Law," Legal Responsibility, 1968-1969; Undated (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Research: Chapter 9 - "Courts and Law," Massachusetts Crime Rates and Juvenile Crime Rates, 1967-1969; Undated (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Research: Chapter 9 - "Courts and Law," Miranda Decisions (1 of 2), 1963-1969; Undated (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Research: Chapter 9 - "Courts and Law," Miranda Decisions (2 of 2), 1963-1969; Undated (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Research: Chapter 9 - "Courts and Law," Orlando Delli Paoli Case/Bruton Case, 1968-1969; Undated (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Research: Chapter 9 - "Courts and Law," Overcriminalization, 1967-1969; Undated (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Research: Chapter 9 - "Courts and Law," Overrulings-Reversals, 1967-1968; Undated (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Research: Chapter 9 - "Courts and Law," Penal Code Reform, 1969 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Research: Chapter 9 - "Courts and Law," Pornography/Obscenity, 1967-1969; Undated (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Research: Chapter 9 - "Courts and Law," Powell v. Texas, 1968-1969 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Research: Chapter 9 - "Courts and Law," Report on Overcrowding in New York City Jails, 1969 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Research: Chapter 9 - "Courts and Law," Sentencing, 1968 (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Research: Chapter 9 - "Courts and Laws," Simplicity/ Complexity, 1967; Undated (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Research: Chapter 9 - "Courts and Law," Stop and Frisk, 1968-1969 (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Research: Chapter 9 - "Courts and Law," Supreme Court, 1967-1969; Undated (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - Research: Chapter 9 - "Courts and Law," Supreme Court Trends Since Map v. Ohio, 1967-1968; Undated (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - Research: Chapter 9 - "Courts and Law," Vandalism, 1967-1969 (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - Research: Chapter 10 - "Corrections", 1966-1968; Undated (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - Research: Chapter 10 - "Corrections", 1968-1969; Undated (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - Research: Chapter 10 - "Corrections," Bucks County Prison-Penn., 1968-1969; Undated (Box 10, Folder 23)
  - Research: Chapter 10 - "Corrections," Community Action Grant Proposal, ca. 1966 (Box 10, Folder 24)
  - Research: Chapter 10 - "Corrections," Correctional Facilities (1 of 2), 1960-1969; Undated (Box 10, Folder 25)
  - Research: Chapter 10 - "Corrections," Correctional Facilities (2 of 2), 1960-1969; Undated (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Research: Chapter 10 - "Corrections," Federal Prisons (1 of 2), 1967-1969 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Research: Chapter 10 - "Corrections," Federal Prisons (2 of 2), 1967-1969 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Research: Chapter 10 - "Corrections," Journal Articles (1 of 3), 1958-1967 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Research: Chapter 10 - "Corrections," Journal Articles (2 of 3), 1958-1967 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Research: Chapter 10 - "Corrections," Journal Articles (3 of 3), 1958-1967 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Research: Chapter 10 - "Corrections," LEAA Grants and Contracts Strategies for Meeting Correctional Training Manpower Needs, ca. 1965 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Research: Chapter 10 - "Corrections," New York State Board of Parole and Dept. of Mental Hygiene Reports, 1966; Undated (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Research: Chapter 10 - "Corrections," New York State Dept. of Corrections Report, 1966 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Research: Chapter 10 - "Corrections," Notes and Outlines, 1967-1969; Undated (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Research: Chapter 10 - "Corrections," Office of Probation, 1967-1968; Undated (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Research: Chapter 10 - "Corrections," Parole, 1966-1969; Undated (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Research: Chapter 10 - "Corrections," Probation, 1966-1969; Undated (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Research: Chapter 10 - "Corrections," Proposals, 1966 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Research: Chapter 10 - "Corrections," Reports from New York State Training Schools and Division for Youth (1 of 2), 1965-1966 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Research: Chapter 10 - "Corrections," Reports from New York State Training Schools and Division for Youth (2 of 2), 1965-1966 (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Research: Chapter 10 - "Corrections," Reports on Alternative Methods, 1964-1968 (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - Research: Chapter 10 - "Corrections," Speeches and New Clippings, 1964-1968; Undated (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - Research: Chapter 10 - "Corrections," Speeches by Director of U.S. Bureau of Prisons M. Alexander (1 of 2), 1965-1968 (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - Research: Chapter 10 - "Corrections," Speeches by Director of U.S. Bureau of Prisons M. Alexander (2 of 2), 1965-1968 (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - Research: Chapter 10 - "Corrections," Values, 1968-1969; Undated (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - Research: Chapter 11 - "A System," Status Report Notes, 1967-1968; Undated (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - Research: Chapter 13 - "The Murk of Crime Causation," Biological (Physical Causation), 1968-1970; Undated (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - Research: Chapter 13 - "The Murk of Crime Causation," Journal Articles and Newsclippings (1 of 4), 1964-1968 (Box 11, Folder 24)
  - Research: Chapter 13 - "The Murk of Crime Causation," Journal Articles and Newsclippings (2 of 4), 1964-1968 (Box 11, Folder 25)
  - Research: Chapter 13 - "The Murk of Crime Causation," Journal Articles and Newsclippings (3 of 4), 1964-1968 (Box 11, Folder 26)
  - Research: Chapter 13 - "The Murk of Crime Causation," Journal Articles and Newsclippings (4 of 4), 1964-1968 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Research: Chapter 13 - "The Murk of Crime Causation," Narcotics and Alcohol, 1965; Undated (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Research: Chapter 13 - "The Murk of Crime Causation," Notes on Criminology, 1966-1967; Undated (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Research: Chapter 13 - "The Murk of Crime Causation," Notes and Newsclippings, 1967-1968; Undated (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Research: Chapter 13 - "The Murk of Crime Causation," Notes and Newsclippings (1 of 2), 1968 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Research: Chapter 13 - "The Murk of Crime Causation," Notes and Newsclippings (2 of 2), 1968 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Research: Chapter 13 - "The Murk of Crime Causation," Notes, Newsclippings, Journal Articles, 1968-1969 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Research: Chapter 14 - "What is Crime?" Alcohol Journal Articles, 1963-1968 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Research: Chapter 14 - "What is Crime?" Manhattan Bowery Project (1 of 2), 1967-1969 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Research: Chapter 14 - "What is Crime?" Manhattan Bowery Project (2 of 2), 1967-1969 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Research: Chapter 14 - "What is Crime?" Newsclippings, 1963-1969; Undated (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Research: Chapter 14 - "What is Crime?" Newsclippings and Notes, 1957-1969 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Research: Chapter 14 - "What is Crime" - Notes On Bayview Rehabilitation Center, 1968-1969 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Research: Chapter 14 - "What is Crime?" Notes and Outlines, Undated (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Research: Chapter 14 - "What is Crime?" NYS - Narcotic Addiction Control Commission (NACC) (1 of 2), 1966-1969; Undated (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Research: Chapter 14 - "What is Crime?" NYS - Narcotic Addiction Control Commission (NACC) (2 of 2), 1966-1969; Undated (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Research: Chapter 14 - "What is Crime?" NYS - NACC 1st Annual Statistical Report, 1968 (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Research: Chapter 14 - "What is Crime?" NYS - NAAC Pamphlets and Report (1 of 2), 1968; Undated (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - Research: Chapter 14 - "What is Crime?" - NYS - NAAC Pamphlets and Reports (2 of 2), 1968; Undated (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Research: Chapter 14 - "What is Crime?" Phoenix House, 1968-1969; Undated (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Research: Chapter 14 - "What is Crime?" Research, Alcohol and Highway/Safety, 1968 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Research: Chapter 14 - "What is Crime?" Treatment and Rehabilitation Centers, 1968-1969; Undated (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Research: Chapter 15 - "Power," Correspondence, Notes, and Outlines, 1967-1968; Undated (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Research: Chapter 15 - "Power," Grants, 1967-1969 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Research: Chapter 15 - "Power", Juvenile Delinquency and Crime Control at the State and Local Levels, 1965; 1968 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Research: Chapter 15 - "Power," Legislative Aid, 1959; 1969 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Research: Chapter 15 - "Power", Local Government, 1967; Undated (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Research: Chapter 15 - "Power," National Improvements to Law Enforcement, 1968-1969 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Research: Chapter 15 - "Power," Press Releases, Journal Articles, Newsclippings, 1967-1969; Undated (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Research: Chapter 15 - "Power," Press Releases, Journal Articles, Newsclippings, 1968-1969; Undated (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Research: Chapter 15 - "Power," Program to Meet Maryland's Fiscal Problems, 1967 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Research: Chapter 15 - "Power," Report on Crime in New Jersey, 1967-1969; Undated (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Research: Chapter 15 - "Power," Report on Crime in Florida, 1967-1969; Undated (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - Research: Chapter 15 - "Power," State Dept. of Crime Control, 1967; Undated (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - Research: Chapter 15 - "Power," States - Consolidation and Organization, 1966-1969; Undated (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - Research: Chapter 15 - "Power," Various County Police Departments, 1968; Undated (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - Research: Chapter 16 - "A Restructuring," Major Suggestions, 1967-1969; Undated (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - Research: Chapter 16 - "A Restructuring," Notes, Outlines, and Articles, 1968-1969; Undated (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - Research: Chapter 16 - "A Restructuring," Research on the Justice System (1 of 2), 1968-1969; Undated (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - Research: Chapter 16 - "A Restructuring," Research on the Justice System (2 of 2), 1968-1969; Undated (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - Research: Chapter 17 - "Citizen Action," "The Annals of Legislation: The Turning Point", 1968 (Box 13, Folder 22)
  - Research: Chapter 17 - "Citizen Action, The Citizen's Role (1 of 2), 1960; 1967-1969; Undated (Box 13, Folder 23)
  - Research: Chapter 17 - "Citizen Action," The Citizen's Role (2 of 2), 1960; 1967-1969; Undated (Box 13, Folder 24)
  - Research: Chapter 17 - "Citizen Action," Constitutional Limits and Citizen Rights, 1967-1969; Undated (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Research: Chapter 17 - "Citizen Action, Interview w/Ramsey Clark, 1969 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Research: Chapter 17 - "Citizen Action," Notes, and Outlines, 1969; Undated (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Research: Chapter 17 - "Citizen Action," Notes and Outlines, Undated (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Research: Chapter 18 - "The Dike," Liberal/ Conservative Views, 1968-1969 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Research: Chapter 18 - "The Dike," Notes, 1969; Undated (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Research: Chapter 18 - "The Dike," Notes and Analogies, 1967-1969; Undated (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Research on the FBI (1 of 2), 1967-1969; Undated (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Research on the FBI (2 of 2), 1967-1969; Undated (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Research on Juvenile Delinquency, "The Future of Juvenile Court", 1968 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Research on Riots, 1968-1969 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Research- Remarks of EHL, Annual NYS Conference of Mayors, 1967 June (Box 15, Folder 3)
- Other Publications, 1963-1987; 6; 0.66 cubic ft.
  This series is arranged alphabetically.
  This series contains some of Lumbard’s published materials and other research, including his work on another manuscript with Philip John Stead entitled, “World Criminal Justice Systems.”
  - "Computer - Based Responses to the NYS Criminal Justice Community's Need to Know" by Eliot Lumbard and Charts, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - "The Counselling 'Whipsaw' During Parallel Proceedings", 1979 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - "Encouraging Integrity in Office" - Citizens Union Research Foundations, Inc., 1964 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - "Local and State Action Against Organized Crime", 1963 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - "Local and State Action Against Organized Crime" with Information on State Government Crime Control and Encouraging Integrity in Office, 1963-1964; 1968 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - "Organized Crime and Technology" with Information on Illinois Institute of Technology and the First National Symposium on Law Enforcement and Technology, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - A Philosophy of Public Order- Of Crime Control Notes and Newsclippings, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - A Philosophy of Public Order - Of Crime Control Notes and Newsclippings, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Research -Street Crime Control US Department of Justice, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Research "Teens on Patrol" - Summary, 1967-1968 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - "State and Local Government Control" - Notre Dame Lawyer, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - "Transitional Reorganization: Coping with the Insolvent Multinational"-Presented in Tokyo, 1986 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - World Criminal Justice Systems - Agreement Between Lumbard and Stead, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - World Criminal Justice Systems - Correspondence with Philip Stead, 1979-1987 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - World Criminal Justice Systems Drafts, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - World Criminal Justice Systems Lumbard and Stead Notes and Memos, 1979-1982 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - World Criminal Justice Systems - Lumbard and Stead's Resumes, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - World Criminal Justice System - MacMillian Material, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - World Criminal Justice Systems Research, 1978-1981 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - World Criminal Justice Systems Research, 1981-1984 (Box 2, Folder 11)
- Private Practice, 1951-1999
  This series concerns Lumbard’s career as an attorney where he specialized in general commercial litigation, including serving as legal representation for brokers, investment bankers and on bankruptcy matters. Some of his significant cases were: counsel to Charles Seligson, trustee in bankruptcy of Ira Haupt and Co.; trustee in bankruptcy of Universal Money Order Co., Inc; Chairman of the Board, Palisades Life Insurance Company, formerly Equity Funding Life Insurance Company of New York; special master in admiralty of Hellenic Lines, Ltd.; counsel to Cyprus Minerals Company; trustee in Roy Cohn proceedings. He also represented the New York City abortion clinic, the Center for Reproductive and Sexual Health (CRASH).
  - Cases, 1951-1999
    This subseries includes court proceedings, statements, transcripts, memos, motions, and news clippings.
    - Bolker vs. Leonova - Property Agreement, 1979 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - Breed, Abborr and Morgan - Firm Dinner in Honor of William O. McKnight, 1953 (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - Briefs and Records- Reynolds and Co. Ridgewood, New Jersey, Branch Litigation Appeals Finn Commercial Company v. Reynolds Co. Robert Eichler, First Discount Corporation, Arthur Katz and Leo Sinsheimer Harper-Malone Co., Inc., v. Reynolds and Co. Dembar, Et Al. V. Reynolds and Co. and North Jersey Trust Company Vol. 14, 1962-1966 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Briefs and Records- U.S. A.V. Dunkel, Et Al. Sheldon (Sec/Treas., Local 88, Masters, Mates and Pilots, AFL-CIO) V. Vasko and Kleban Eisenberg V. Hayden, Stone Incorporated Fox V. Peter Kewit Sons Co., Et Al. U.S.A V. Masiello and Stickel TWAV. Civil Aeronautics Board Alonzo V. U.S.A (Amicus Curiae for the Anaconda Co.) People v. Moore Vol. 13, 1951-1968 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - Center for Reproductive and Sexual Health Directory, Undated (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Center For Reproductive and Sexual Health, Inc. (Independent- out - of-Hospital Health Facility) and Community Sex Information and Education Service, Inc. -Not For Profit Corporations Vol. 1, State of New York Department of Health City of New York Department of Health Internal Revenue Service, 1970-1973 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - Center For Reproductive and Sexual Health, Inc. (Independent- out - of-Hospital Health Facility) and Community Sex Information and Education Service, Inc. -Not For Profit Corporations Vol. 2, State of New York Department of Health City of New York Department of Health Internal Revenue Service, 1971-1972 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Charles Seligson, as Trustee in Bankruptcy of IRA Haupt and Co., a Limited Partnership, Bankrupt, vs. The Fidelity and Casualty Company of New York- Subrogation Issues: Third-Party Litigation Involving the American Express Company, 2. Sydney Krause, Trustee for Class A Creditors of D.R. Comenzo and Co., Inc. v. American Guarantee and Liability Insurance Company, 3. Bunge Corporation v. The London and Overseas Insurance Co., et al. Vol. 6, 1967-1968 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Charles Seligson as Trustee in Bankruptcy of IRA Haupt and Co., a Limited Partnership, Bankrupt, vs. The Fidelity and Causality Company of New York - Working Papers for Section 21 (a), Bankruptcy Act Investigative Hearings, Ira Haupt and Co. Partnership Agreement Investigative Accounting Reports, Notice and Proof of Claim Brooker's Blanket Bonds, Complaint, New York Supreme Court New York County Vol. 1, 1964-1965 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Curtis Flood v. Bowie Kuhn, 1972 (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - Cyprus Minerals Company Case: Affidavit of Joel L. Lennen in Support of Claimant's Motion for Partial Summary Judgement, 1989 January (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Cyprus Minerals Company Case- Affidavit of M. William Mono in Opposition to Cyprus' Motion for Partial Summary Judgement, 1989 January (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Cyprus Minerals Company Case- Claimants First Document and Interrogatories Request and Debtor's/Counter Claimant's, 1989 January (Box 6, Folder 7)